[{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981203093,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":12852,"timeElapsed":424607},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981208947,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":5852,"timeElapsed":430461},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981220842,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":11893,"timeElapsed":442356},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981239898,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":19054,"timeElapsed":461412},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981288523,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":48623,"timeElapsed":510037},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981317685,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":29160,"timeElapsed":539199},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981331761,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":14075,"timeElapsed":553275},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981353744,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":21981,"timeElapsed":575258},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981377329,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":23583,"timeElapsed":598843},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981405589,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":24962,"timeElapsed":627103},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981411818,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":6227,"timeElapsed":633332},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981416812,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":4992,"timeElapsed":638326},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981442570,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":25756,"timeElapsed":664084},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981489554,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":46982,"timeElapsed":711068},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981499497,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":9942,"timeElapsed":721011},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981542587,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":43088,"timeElapsed":764101},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981555468,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":12878,"timeElapsed":776982},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981560100,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":4630,"timeElapsed":781613},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981618656,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":56240,"timeElapsed":840169},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981645485,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":26827,"timeElapsed":866999},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981682546,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":37060,"timeElapsed":904060},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981718578,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":36030,"timeElapsed":940092},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981752553,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":33973,"timeElapsed":974067},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981802213,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":49658,"timeElapsed":1023727},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981826281,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":24066,"timeElapsed":1047795},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981850395,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":24112,"timeElapsed":1071909},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981890326,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":39929,"timeElapsed":1111840},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981914967,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":24639,"timeElapsed":1136481},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982032705,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":116216,"timeElapsed":1254219},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982037499,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":4792,"timeElapsed":1259013},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982041351,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":3850,"timeElapsed":1262865},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982045885,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":4532,"timeElapsed":1267399},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982050861,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":4974,"timeElapsed":1272375},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982099939,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":49076,"timeElapsed":1321453},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982104063,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":4122,"timeElapsed":1325577},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982107945,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":3881,"timeElapsed":1329459},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982111153,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":3206,"timeElapsed":1332667},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982147279,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":33332,"timeElapsed":1368793},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982151723,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":4442,"timeElapsed":1373237},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982155725,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":4000,"timeElapsed":1377239},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982161804,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":6078,"timeElapsed":1383318},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982168347,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":6540,"timeElapsed":1389861},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982186057,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":17708,"timeElapsed":1407571},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982190225,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":4166,"timeElapsed":1411739},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982195051,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":4823,"timeElapsed":1416565},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982199599,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":4546,"timeElapsed":1421113},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982276475,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":75562,"timeElapsed":1497989},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982281425,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":4948,"timeElapsed":1502939},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982284713,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3286,"timeElapsed":1506227},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982288138,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3424,"timeElapsed":1509652},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982291567,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3427,"timeElapsed":1513081},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982358513,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":66943,"timeElapsed":1580027},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982363228,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":4714,"timeElapsed":1584742},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982369691,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":6460,"timeElapsed":1591205},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982377016,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":7324,"timeElapsed":1598530},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982428983,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":50705,"timeElapsed":1650497},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982431903,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":2918,"timeElapsed":1653417},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982434544,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2638,"timeElapsed":1656058},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982436858,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2312,"timeElapsed":1658372},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982442453,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":5593,"timeElapsed":1663967},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982467777,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":25322,"timeElapsed":1689291},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982471192,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":3414,"timeElapsed":1692706},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982475056,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":3862,"timeElapsed":1696570},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982478714,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":3656,"timeElapsed":1700228},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982597156,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":117264,"timeElapsed":1818670},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982602094,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":4936,"timeElapsed":1823608},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982605690,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":3594,"timeElapsed":1827204},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982609652,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":3959,"timeElapsed":1831166},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982613728,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":4074,"timeElapsed":1835242},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982626538,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":12807,"timeElapsed":1848052},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982631798,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":5255,"timeElapsed":1853312},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982634752,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":2951,"timeElapsed":1856266},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982640312,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":5558,"timeElapsed":1861826},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982714875,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":72986,"timeElapsed":1936389},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982718096,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":3218,"timeElapsed":1939610},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982721436,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":3338,"timeElapsed":1942950},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982725027,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":3589,"timeElapsed":1946541},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982729110,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":4081,"timeElapsed":1950624},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982774771,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":45659,"timeElapsed":1996284},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982786252,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":11479,"timeElapsed":2007766},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982795700,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":9446,"timeElapsed":2017214},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982801057,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":5355,"timeElapsed":2022571},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982810098,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":9039,"timeElapsed":2031612},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982850550,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":39204,"timeElapsed":2072064},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982853158,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2606,"timeElapsed":2074672},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982856431,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":3272,"timeElapsed":2077945},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982860108,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3675,"timeElapsed":2081622},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982865372,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":5261,"timeElapsed":2086886},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982907700,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":42326,"timeElapsed":2129214},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982910648,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2946,"timeElapsed":2132162},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982914838,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":4188,"timeElapsed":2136352},{"subjectID":"gfp75gluqf","prolificID":"6660bd37bb0400179789f595","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b252e86159535b282b6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982917774,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2934,"timeElapsed":2139288}]